Voudouris Angelos - Michael

DATA SCIENTIST Junior

About Me

I am student 5th year Undergraduate Student and for a year now i have experience in **Big-Data** and **Supervised-Learning**. I started taking my first steps from Kaggle where I took my first classification model. Later I started working with regression models in **time series forecasting** Crude Oil WTI.

Software

Python

C (Programming Language)

SQL

JavaScript

Skills

Web Scrapping

Time – Series Analysis

Data Understanding

Bootstrap Method

Machine Learning Models

Model Selection

Gradient Boosting

Communication







Military Obligations

Hellenic Army / Special Forces Specialty of Transmissions

Work Experience

2021 Machine Learning - ML Oil Trading

- Collaboration with Daniil Kiose Quantitative Modelling & Analytics at Standard Chartered Bank
- Web scraping a time series of US commodity
- Data preparation
- Forecast Crude Oil WTI with NGBoost model

2021 E - Commerce Website

- Worked with Raphael Kargos, undergraduate seminar for the university
- Create a dynamic website E Commerce
 HTML, JavaScript, MySQL
 Click <u>here</u>

2020- 2021 Wordpress Website

- Wordpress builder & designer for online massage service by Yoan Agar
- Research for more economical hosting Click <u>here</u>

2012 - 2021 Family Business Management

Voudouris Pastry - Cafe
Achladochori in Serres, Greece
(For the summer seasons)
Click here

Education

2016 - 2021

School of Science, Department of Informatics and Computer Technology, in Kastoria, in the North West part of Greece

5rd year Undergraduate Student